Let's take a quick look at the latest features of Kerlo 2025.2
First, we developed a piece of paper editor and expanded Kerlo's needle design function
Select the wool product, then click the wool ball icon next to the needle
Here you will be able to accurately design the piece of paper
Adjust the density of the piece of paper and the thickness of the gusset, and apply different types of needles
Then simulate and apply it to the costume
You can preview the style effect after applying different needles
We have added more types for the piece of paper
Now you can easily make pants and shorts
For pants, we have two options, gold waist pants and leisure pants
You can create a piece of paper by entering a simple measurement value
As shown here
Now select the leisure pants
You can switch to setting detailed information
This allows you to enter more details to increase control and accuracy
You can also use the AI version generator to create pants and shorts
For shorts, you can choose between round shorts and A-shaped shorts
Enter the text prompt
Create an image, then use the image to create your version
Or you can also upload a style image and generate the corresponding version
Now you can use the GPU to simulate a software model
Compared to before, faster and more accurate test version and edit costume
Open the software model simulation, use GPU simulation
You can check the body change
We have updated the cutout size
To make the size of the cutout more accurate
Now when you open the cutout
You can check all the cutouts on the size of the cutout
And you can control the cutout position of each size
You can also change the direction of the cutout size
And the fixed size
Now it's easier for you to create a repeat pattern
We have updated the editor
It allows you to quickly and easily
The horizontal and vertical even flip the image at the same time
We have updated the 2D position measurement in the sticker attribute editor
It allows you to move the sticker by entering the exact position value
Put your sticker in the exact position you want
Now you just need to right-click on the zipper
And select the version that is copied to the symmetrical modification
You can easily create a symmetrical zipper
But the zipper on both sides is not linked
You can edit the zipper on either side
We heard that many users
I hope I can stop the new cutout window on the left side
So now you can click on this arrow
Move the cutout back to its original position
After this update, the cutout will be removed
Now you can easily use MetaHuman in the cutout
Design
Use the DNA file format to import different bodies and heads
So that it is in line with Unreal Engine and other platforms
Once you have completed the design in the cutout
You can export all the content back to MetaHuman Creator
Your clothing will automatically adjust the size
To adapt to any changes you make to the MetaHuman body
So that it is easier to use MetaHuman than before
You can also change the size of your clothes
To make it easier to use MetaHuman
Create a realistic rendering image
We are very happy to announce that in this version
We will expand the customized configuration function to the hat category
You only need to select the corresponding version or OBJ file
Then register it as a hat
After registration
You can add this hat to any of your projects
In addition, we have also updated the design configuration in the cutout
Expanded it to the customized copper model
You can change the colors here, including hair, glasses, eyebrows, underwear, skin, etc.
We have added some functions to improve the user experience in the animation
Now you just need to click a button to create layers for all objects
You can also add layers to your project
We also added the option of shape optimization, plate shrinkage and pressure
This update simplifies the operation of adding keyframes
Allow you to add multiple keyframes at a time
And you can choose to apply the keyframe to all layers or select a layer
Thank you very much for watching
I wish you a pleasant creation in the hole